Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box 39, Folder (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Where Each Dollar Went, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: GM Corporaion Newsletter, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Development Program for Stenographers, Typists & Clerks, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Why Cadillac Operates a Suggestion System, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
    By J. M. Roche. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Grievance Procedure, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Seniority Agreement Between New Departure Division and the UAW-CIO Local 626, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Seniority Agreement Between Harrison Radiator Division, General Motors Corporation and G. M. Unit No. 1, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: For Your Protection, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Box 39, Folder (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Development and Growth of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Harlow Curtice. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Personnel Function and its Benefits to Plant Management, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Your GM Savings-Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Your GM Savings - Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: General Motors Savings - Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: AC Sales Inventory and Examiner's Manual, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Statistical Methods in Quality Control, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Principles of Creative Activity, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Supplemental Agreement Covering Supplemental Unemploymens Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Supplemental Agreements Covering Pension Plan Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Local Agreements between AC Spark Plug Division and Local 651, UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the Pattern Makers' League of North America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Supplemental Agreement Covering Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Local Agreements Between Buick Motor Division and Local 599 UAW, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Supplemental Agreement covering Pension Plan and Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Supplemental Agreement Covering Pension Plan and Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Supplemental Agreement Covering Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Work and Work Standards at Buick, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: A Look at the Buick Supervisor's Safety Job, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Local Wage Agreements Between AC Spark Plug Division and Local 651, UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Supplemental Agreements Covering Pension Plan and Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Designed for General Motors Salaried Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Your Inurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Designed for General Motors ourly-Rate Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Designed for General Motor Hourly-Rate Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: 1955 Press Conference, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: A Look at GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: How the Sub Plan Will Apply at GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Your Extra Benefits, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: How GM Operates Without UAW Pact, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Detroit, Michigan. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Delco Radio Broadcaster, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Supplemental Agreement to National Agreement, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: To The Men and Women of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Information Bulletin for GM Editors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Previews of GM Posters, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Summary of Service Recognition Plans, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Previews of posters, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 41: Tuning in Delco Radio Division, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Ten Years of industrial Peace at GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: I'm with GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: General Motors retirement Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Your GM Pension, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Reply of General Motors President to President of UAW, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Ladle, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 48: The Greatest Frontier, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 49: There's a Right Way for Every Job, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 50: Your GM Pension, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 51: GMAC and You, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 52: How can You Lose?, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 53: General motors, 50 Million Cars, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 54: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 55: Agreement Between Genetal Motors Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Box 40, Folder 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Information Concerning the UAW-CIO Strike at General Motors, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: TrainingProgram for Potential Foremen, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Production Shop Manual, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The Truth is That, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Standard Apprentice Plan, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Standard Apprentice Plan, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Organizations and Functions of the Personnel Division, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Rating of Foreman, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Program for Safe-Guarding Punch Press Operations, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Safety Questionnaire for New Employees, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Apprentice Training Manual, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Minimum Standards for Safe Plant Operation, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Executive Training Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Working With Individuals, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Judging Procedure for My Job Contest, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Outline of Apprentice Training Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Company Releases on UAW-CIO Strike, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: The Responsibility of Management, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: General Information and Basic Policies Affecting AC Factory Employees, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: General Motors Industrial Hygiene Service, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Health Maintenance Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Reports and Recommendations of the President's Fact-Finding Board, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Report and Recommendations of the President's Fact-Finding Board, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Wage Agreement, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: When Labor Strikes Everybody Losts, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: When Labor Strikes Everybody Loses, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Seniority Agreement Between Local 653, UAW-CIO and Potiac Motor Division, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: General Motors Reply to UAW-CIO Brief Submitted in Support of Wage Demand, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: You and Your Job at New Departure, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: The Story of Fisher Body, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Executive Training Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: The College Graduate and General Motors, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Your Job at New Departure, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Educational Assistance for GM Employees, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: The General Motors Strikes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: A Case Example in Public Relations, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
    By Paul Garrett. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Recognition of Loyalty & Service at New Departure, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: MCJ Accentuating the Positive, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America - CIO, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Working Together, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: General Instructions, Safety Rules, Fire Instructions, Personnel Policies, Shop Rules, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: How Industry Has Prepared for its Returning Servicemen, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: Management Responsibility for Discipline, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
    By H. W. Anderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: Rules and regulations and General Instructions for the Plant Protection Department, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: General Motors Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 47: Agreement Between General Motors corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: Working With Genera; Motors, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 50: Retirement Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: Choosing a Career, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Management Responsibility for Safety, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
    By David Mould. Item is in English.
- Box 40, Folder (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Chronology of the GM-UAW Case, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Seniority Agreement, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The General Motors Medical Program for Health and Safety, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
    By C. D. Selby. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: General Motors' Comments on Certain Statements Made by Walter P. Reuther Before the Senate Committee on Education and Labor, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: General Motors' Statement Before Fact Finding Board, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Detroit Transmission Division Executive Bulletin, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Placement and Follow-up Record, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Organization Chart Fisher Body Division, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Frigidaire at War, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Is Loyalty an "Either" - or "Proposition"?, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Executive Training Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: What Does the Panel Think? What Does General Motors Think? What Do You Think?, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: New Departure Program for Hiring and Introducing Personnel to Their Jobs, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Man to Man on the Job, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: The Veteran Back in G. M., Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Text of a Statement Made to the Senate War Investigation Committee, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
    By H.W. Anderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: General Motors Corporation and UAW-CIO Negotiations on 30% Wage Demand Beginning August 1945, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Outline of Functions of the Educational Department, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Victory Continuity, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: A Veteran Returns to New Departure, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: General Motors Corporation Rehabilitation Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: An Analysis of the Paid Sick Leave Plan for Hourly-Rated Factory Womans, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Purchasing Power for Prosperity, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: As Johnny Comes Marching Home, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Buick Veterans Your Job, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: The Use of Tests in Improving Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: ABC of Hand Tools, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Life at Frigidaire, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: The Foreman's Place in Management Under the Free Enterprise System, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Your Safety, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Safety Instructions, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Should Management be Unionized, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Employees' Handbook of Information Shop Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Safety in Grinding, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Minefields, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: General Motors Post-War Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: Management - Tell What You Stand for!, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: General Motors Employees Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Safety Deposit Book for Employees, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Box 41, Folder (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    A General Motors Training Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Book 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Book 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Better Methods Block Book 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Better Methods Block Book 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Better Methods Block Book 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Introductory Block Manual. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Introductory Block. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Work Standards, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Approaching an Individual Block. Item is in English.
- Box 41, Folder (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Motors Executive Training Program, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Decisoin of Umpore Willard E. Hotchkiss in Tar Barrel Case, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Bigger and Better in Everything, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Executive Training Program, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Procedure for Employment Survey, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Memorandum of Settlement of Strike of Tool and Die Makers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Fisher Body Division Departmental Problems, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: DTD Supervisory Evaluation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Talk at the Twenty Sixth Meeting od the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
    By W. S. Knudsen. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Conference of Personnel Directors and Educational Leaders, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Agreements Between General motors Corp and the United Automobile Workers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Agreements Between General Motors Corp and the United Automobile Workers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Address Before the Houston Chamber of Commerce, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
    By William Knudsen. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: News and Views, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Standard Apprentice Plan, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Correspondence Between the President of the UAW and Officers of General Motors Corp. Regarding Organizing Activities, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Apprentice Training Program, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Employees' Association and Works Council, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: How to Create a Labor Shortage, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
    By Charles Kettering. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Look to the Foreman, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: How Members of the General Motors Family are Made Partners, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: A Message to General Motors Employes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Public Relations - Industry's No. 1 Job, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Cadillac Employees Association, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Plan for Employee Representation and Works Council, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Production Control, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Supervision's Job in 1934, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Buick Employees' Association, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Suggestions for the Safe Operation and Care of Electric and Locomotive Cranes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Purchasing, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Fisher Flashes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Petition for Investigation and Certification of Representatives Pursuant to the Provisions of the National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Buick Employees' Association, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Employees' Savings and Investment Plan of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Employees' Savings and Investment Plan of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: An Explanation of the Savings Plan, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: A Rainy Day, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: General Motors Strike, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Shall we ave More or Less?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Bonus Plan of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: Employees' Association and Works Council, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: What is a Job?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: It's a Deal, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 48: 1939 Employe Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: General Motors, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: A Message to Our Employees on Progress of the Strike Situation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 52: Report of the Council for Executive Development, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 53: General Motors Employees Contributory Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 54: General Motors Labor Policies and Procedures, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 55: Agreement Between General Motors Corporaation and the International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 56: Safety, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 57: The Sloan Award, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 58: A Message to Stockholders of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 59: A Statement of General Motors Corporation's Basic Policies Governing its Relations with Factory Employees, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 60: Wage-Incentives, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 61: Our Responsibility as Key-Men, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 62: More and Better Jobs, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 63: Men Industry and Common Sense, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Box 42, Folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Changing Challenge, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Policy Regarding Nondiscrimination in Employment, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Working With General Motors, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The College Graduate and General Motors, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your General Motors Retirement Program, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Newsletter to the Stockholders, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: General Motors Motion Pictures, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The General Motors Insurance Program, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Your Blue Cross Benefits, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Your General Motors Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Program, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: For a Better Tomorrow, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Your GM Savings-Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: General Motors: Beyond the Marketplace, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The Harvard Crimson, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Progress Toward Pollution-free Cars, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: A Big Help, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: A Guater Century of Progress, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: 99.86% Safe, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: A Look at Safety in GM, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Jobs and Energy, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: The Answer to the Imports, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: One to One, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
    A Formula for Individual Involvement in Improving Urban Life. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: An Address by James M. Roche, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
    By James Roche. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Heart of the Matter is Opportunity, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: The Role of Business in Solving Social Problems, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Industry's Role in Environmental Management, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: The Year in Review, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: An Automobile Man Looks Ahead, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: A Look at GM, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Agreemen Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)